
LineNumber Line                                                                                                        
---------- ----                                                                                                        
         5     "item_name": "Revision Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                          
       140     "item_name": "EPI Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                                 
       155     "item_name": "Omega Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                             
       290     "item_name": "Ascendancy Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                          
       305     "item_name": "Bass Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                              
       440     "item_name": "Resonance Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                           
       455     "item_name": "Hound Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                             
       590     "item_name": "Command Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                             
       605     "item_name": "Zero-G Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                            
       740     "item_name": "Horizon Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                             
       755     "item_name": "Magnet Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                            
       890     "item_name": "Mech Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                                
       905     "item_name": "Counterweight Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                     
      1040     "item_name": "Bastion Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                             
      1055     "item_name": "Stutter Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                           
      1190     "item_name": "Echo Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                                
      1205     "item_name": "Briar Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                             
      1340     "item_name": "Nature Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                              
      1355     "item_name": "Ignition Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                          
      1490     "item_name": "Avatar Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                              
        17       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
        18       "Enter Aerie of the Dawnshield, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
        20       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
        22     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
        25     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
        28     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
        30     "godly_reward_item_name": "Revision Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                             
        50       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
        51       "Enter Stormglass War Room, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
        53       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
        55     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
        58     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
        61     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
        83       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
        84       "Enter Highdock Crown, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
        87       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
        89     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
        92     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
        95     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       117       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       118       "Enter Founder Seat Chamber, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
       121       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       123     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       126     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       129     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       151       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       152       "Enter Oath-Ring Observatory, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
       153       "Push into Aerie of the Dawnshield and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timel...
       154       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       156     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       159     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       162     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       184       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       185       "Enter Aerie of the Dawnshield, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
       188       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       190     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       193     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       196     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       218       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       219       "Enter Stormglass War Room, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
       221       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       223     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       226     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       229     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       251       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       252       "Enter Highdock Crown, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       255       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       257     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       260     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       263     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       285       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       286       "Enter Founder Seat Chamber, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
       288       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       290     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       293     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       296     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       318       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       319       "Enter Oath-Ring Observatory, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
       322       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       324     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       327     "scheme_vector": "The First-Second Cell of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to rewrite the Sky W...
       330     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       332     "godly_reward_item_name": "EPI Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                    
       352       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       353       "Enter Cloud Barracks, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       355       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       357     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       360     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       363     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       365     "godly_reward_item_name": "Omega Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                
       385       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       386       "Enter Living Garden Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
       388       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       390     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       393     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       396     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       418       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       419       "Enter Skyship Hangar, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       422       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       424     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       427     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       430     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       452       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       453       "Enter Aether Thruster Bay, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
       456       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       458     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       461     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       464     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       486       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       487       "Enter Aerie Infirmary Spire, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
       488       "Push into Cloud Barracks and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timelines are ...
       489       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       491     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       494     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       497     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       519       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       520       "Enter Cloud Barracks, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       523       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       525     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       528     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       531     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       553       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       554       "Enter Living Garden Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
       556       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       558     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       561     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       564     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       586       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       587       "Enter Skyship Hangar, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       590       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       592     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       595     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       598     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       620       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       621       "Enter Aether Thruster Bay, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
       623       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       625     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       628     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       631     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       653       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       654       "Enter Aerie Infirmary Spire, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
       657       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       659     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       662     "scheme_vector": "The Oathless Wing of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to seed false recruits a...
       665     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       667     "godly_reward_item_name": "Ascendancy Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                             
       687       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       688       "Enter Resonant Peaks, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       690       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       692     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       695     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       698     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       700     "godly_reward_item_name": "Bass Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                 
       720       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       721       "Enter Sonic Badlands, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       723       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       725     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       728     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       731     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       753       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       754       "Enter Rhyming Labyrinths, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
       757       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       759     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       762     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       765     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       787       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       788       "Enter Phonetic Wastes, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize...
       791       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       793     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       796     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       799     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       821       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       822       "Enter Whispering Glade, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabiliz...
       823       "Push into Resonant Peaks and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timelines are ...
       824       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       826     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       829     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       832     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       854       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       855       "Enter Resonant Peaks, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       858       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       860     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       863     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       866     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       888       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       889       "Enter Sonic Badlands, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize ...
       891       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       893     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       896     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       899     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       921       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       922       "Enter Rhyming Labyrinths, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
       925       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       927     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       930     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       933     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       955       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       956       "Enter Phonetic Wastes, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize...
       958       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       960     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       963     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
       966     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
       988       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
       989       "Enter Whispering Glade, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabiliz...
       992       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
       994     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
       997     "scheme_vector": "The Backward Bell Choir of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to turn sonic navi...
      1000     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1002     "godly_reward_item_name": "Resonance Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                              
      1022       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1023       "Enter Sparrowhook Flight Lane, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      1025       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1027     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1030     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1033     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1035     "godly_reward_item_name": "Hound Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                
      1055       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1056       "Enter Tempest Frigate Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1058       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1060     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1063     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1066     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1088       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1089       "Enter Stormglass Carrier Bay, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      1092       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1094     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1097     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1100     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1122       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1123       "Enter Warden Horizon Command Ark, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, an...
      1126       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1128     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1131     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1134     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1156       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1157       "Enter Aerie Kennel Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      1158       "Push into Sparrowhook Flight Lane and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timel...
      1159       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1161     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1164     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1167     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1189       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1190       "Enter Sparrowhook Flight Lane, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      1193       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1195     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1198     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1201     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1223       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1224       "Enter Tempest Frigate Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1226       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1228     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1231     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1234     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1256       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1257       "Enter Stormglass Carrier Bay, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      1260       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1262     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1265     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1268     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1290       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1291       "Enter Warden Horizon Command Ark, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, an...
      1293       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1295     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1298     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1301     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1323       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1324       "Enter Aerie Kennel Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      1327       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1329     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1332     "scheme_vector": "The Leash-Cutter Lodge of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to break convoy dis...
      1335     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1337     "godly_reward_item_name": "Command Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                
      1357       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1358       "Enter Orbital Tether Station, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      1360       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1362     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1365     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1368     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1370     "godly_reward_item_name": "Zero-G Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                               
      1390       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1391       "Enter Lunar Readiness Base, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1393       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1395     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1398     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1401     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1423       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1424       "Enter Planet Defense Perimeter, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      1427       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1429     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1432     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1435     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1457       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1458       "Enter Debris Crown, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      1461       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1463     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1466     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1469     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1491       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1492       "Enter Shattered Solar Array, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      1493       "Push into Orbital Tether Station and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timeli...
      1494       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1496     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1499     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1502     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1524       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1525       "Enter Orbital Tether Station, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      1528       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1530     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1533     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1536     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1558       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1559       "Enter Lunar Readiness Base, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1561       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1563     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1566     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1569     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1591       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1592       "Enter Planet Defense Perimeter, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      1595       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1597     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1600     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1603     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1625       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1626       "Enter Debris Crown, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      1628       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1630     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1633     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1636     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1658       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1659       "Enter Shattered Solar Array, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      1662       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1664     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1667     "scheme_vector": "The Hundredth Horizon of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to weaponize orbital...
      1670     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1672     "godly_reward_item_name": "Horizon Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                
      1692       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1693       "Enter Scrap-Yard Labyrinth, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1695       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1697     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1700     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1703     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1705     "godly_reward_item_name": "Magnet Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                               
      1725       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1726       "Enter Deprecated Repositories, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      1728       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1730     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1733     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1736     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1758       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1759       "Enter EPI-Center, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize the ...
      1762       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1764     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1767     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1770     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1792       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1793       "Enter Marlowe Editing Protocol, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      1796       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1798     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1801     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1804     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1826       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1827       "Enter Skyship Salvage Ring, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1828       "Push into Scrap-Yard Labyrinth and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timeline...
      1829       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1831     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1834     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1837     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1859       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1860       "Enter Scrap-Yard Labyrinth, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1863       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1865     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1868     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1871     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1893       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1894       "Enter Deprecated Repositories, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      1896       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1898     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1901     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1904     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1926       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1927       "Enter EPI-Center, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize the ...
      1930       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1932     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1935     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1938     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1960       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1961       "Enter Marlowe Editing Protocol, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      1963       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1965     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      1968     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      1971     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      1993       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      1994       "Enter Skyship Salvage Ring, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      1997       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      1999     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2002     "scheme_vector": "The Rusted Calendar Syndic of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to hide chronal...
      2005     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2007     "godly_reward_item_name": "Mech Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                   
      2027       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2028       "Enter Planet Defense Perimeter, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      2030       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2032     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2035     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2038     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2040     "godly_reward_item_name": "Counterweight Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                        
      2060       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2061       "Enter Raid-Rush Choke Points, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      2063       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2065     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2068     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2071     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2093       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2094       "Enter Magma-Core Forges, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      2097       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2099     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2102     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2105     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2127       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2128       "Enter Molten Forge, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      2131       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2133     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2136     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2139     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2161       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2162       "Enter Bastion Anchor Yard, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
      2163       "Push into Planet Defense Perimeter and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their time...
      2164       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2166     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2169     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2172     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2194       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2195       "Enter Planet Defense Perimeter, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      2198       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2200     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2203     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2206     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2228       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2229       "Enter Raid-Rush Choke Points, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      2231       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2233     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2236     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2239     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2261       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2262       "Enter Magma-Core Forges, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      2265       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2267     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2270     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2273     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2295       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2296       "Enter Molten Forge, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      2298       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2300     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2303     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2306     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2328       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2329       "Enter Bastion Anchor Yard, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
      2332       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2334     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2337     "scheme_vector": "The Era-Break Bastion of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to anchor stolen age...
      2340     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2342     "godly_reward_item_name": "Bastion Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                
      2362       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2363       "Enter Anomaly Ward, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      2365       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2367     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2370     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2373     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2375     "godly_reward_item_name": "Stutter Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                              
      2395       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2396       "Enter Syndicate Spire, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize...
      2398       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2400     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2403     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2406     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2428       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2429       "Enter Front-Matter Void, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      2432       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2434     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2437     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2440     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2462       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2463       "Enter Alternating Archives, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      2466       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2468     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2471     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2474     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2496       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2497       "Enter Null-Mirror Corridor, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      2498       "Push into Anomaly Ward and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their timelines are re...
      2499       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2501     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2504     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2507     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2529       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2530       "Enter Anomaly Ward, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize th...
      2533       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2535     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2538     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2541     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2563       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2564       "Enter Syndicate Spire, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabilize...
      2566       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2568     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2571     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2574     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2596       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2597       "Enter Front-Matter Void, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabili...
      2600       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2602     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2605     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2608     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2630       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2631       "Enter Alternating Archives, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      2633       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2635     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2638     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2641     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2663       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2664       "Enter Null-Mirror Corridor, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stab...
      2667       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2669     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2672     "scheme_vector": "The Knife Between Seconds of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assassinate f...
      2675     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2677     "godly_reward_item_name": "Echo Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                   
      2697       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2698       "Enter Emerald Canopy Sanctuary, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      2700       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2702     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2705     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2708     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2710     "godly_reward_item_name": "Briar Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                                
      2730       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2731       "Enter Pachyderm Sanctuaries, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      2733       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2735     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2738     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2741     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2763       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2764       "Enter Canopy Portrait Halls, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      2767       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2769     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2772     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2775     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2797       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2798       "Enter Evolution Arenas, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabiliz...
      2801       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2803     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2806     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2809     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2831       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2832       "Enter Living Garden Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
      2833       "Push into Emerald Canopy Sanctuary and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their time...
      2834       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2836     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2839     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2842     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2864       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2865       "Enter Emerald Canopy Sanctuary, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and ...
      2868       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2870     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2873     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2876     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2898       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2899       "Enter Pachyderm Sanctuaries, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      2901       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2903     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2906     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2909     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2931       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2932       "Enter Canopy Portrait Halls, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and sta...
      2935       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2937     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2940     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2943     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2965       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2966       "Enter Evolution Arenas, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabiliz...
      2968       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      2970     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      2973     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      2976     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      2998       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      2999       "Enter Living Garden Deck, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabil...
      3002       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3004     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3007     "scheme_vector": "The Withered Future Garden of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to infect livin...
      3010     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3012     "godly_reward_item_name": "Nature Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                 
      3020     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3021     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Redacted Black Signal",                                               
      3032       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3033       "Enter Eclipse Engine Heart Remnant, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, ...
      3035       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3037     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3038     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3040     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3043     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3045     "godly_reward_item_name": "Ignition Sovereign Armament of the Sky Wardens",                             
      3048     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 1/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3053     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3054     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Oathless Hidden Ledger",                                              
      3065       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3066       "Enter Dawnforge Understar, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
      3068       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3070     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3071     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3073     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3076     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3081     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 2/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3086     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3087     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Backward False Witness",                                              
      3098       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3099       "Enter Sky Warden Treaty Ring, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      3101       "Confront an operative, construct, or lieutenant-proxy from The Prime Epochalypse Synod, prevent th...
      3102       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3104     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3105     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3107     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3110     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3115     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 3/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3120     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3121     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Hollow Silent Breach",                                                
      3127     "secondary_location": "Epochalypse Engine Core",                                                        
      3132       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3133       "Enter Aerie of the Dawnshield, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      3134       "Push into Epochalypse Engine Core and clear a multi-room Order facility, defeat its elite custodia...
      3135       "Confront an operative, construct, or lieutenant-proxy from The Prime Epochalypse Synod, prevent th...
      3136       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3138     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3139     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3141     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3144     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3149     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 4/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3154     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3155     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Black-Clock Broken Convoy",                                           
      3160     "primary_location": "Epochalypse Engine Core",                                                          
      3166       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3167       "Enter Epochalypse Engine Core, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      3168       "Push into Eclipse Engine Heart Remnant and extract captured Sky Wardens or witnesses before their ...
      3169       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3171     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3172     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3174     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3177     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3182     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 5/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3187     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3188     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Unwritten Counter-Oath",                                              
      3199       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3200       "Enter Eclipse Engine Heart Remnant, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, ...
      3202       "Confront an operative, construct, or lieutenant-proxy from The Prime Epochalypse Synod, prevent th...
      3203       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3205     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3206     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3208     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3211     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3216     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 6/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3221     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3222     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: False-Dawn Mirror Warrant",                                           
      3233       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3234       "Enter Dawnforge Understar, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and stabi...
      3236       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3238     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3239     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3241     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3244     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3249     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 7/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3254     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3255     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Century-Bound Echo Siege",                                            
      3266       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3267       "Enter Sky Warden Treaty Ring, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and st...
      3269       "Confront an operative, construct, or lieutenant-proxy from The Prime Epochalypse Synod, prevent th...
      3270       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3272     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3273     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3275     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3278     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3283     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 8/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3288     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3289     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Broken-Second Secret Trial",                                          
      3295     "secondary_location": "Epochalypse Engine Core",                                                        
      3300       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3301       "Enter Aerie of the Dawnshield, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      3302       "Push into Epochalypse Engine Core and move a living witness, ship core, or oath archive through Or...
      3303       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3305     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3306     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3308     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3311     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3316     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 9/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one a...
      3321     "arc": "The Epochalypse Engine",                                                                        
      3322     "title": "The Epochalypse Engine: Era-Stolen Cell Collapse",                                            
      3327     "primary_location": "Epochalypse Engine Core",                                                          
      3333       "Receive the operation directly from Torinn Rhogar and confirm that the adversary is The Order of t...
      3334       "Enter Epochalypse Engine Core, locate three traces of The Order of the Epochalypse activity, and s...
      3336       "Confront an operative, construct, or lieutenant-proxy from The Prime Epochalypse Synod, prevent th...
      3337       "Return to Torinn Rhogar, deliver the sealed proof against The Order of the Epochalypse, update the...
      3339     "antagonist": "The Order of the Epochalypse",                                                           
      3340     "shadow_cell": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod",                                                           
      3342     "scheme_vector": "The Prime Epochalypse Synod of The Order of the Epochalypse attempts to assemble a ...
      3345     "story_summary": "After the final boss is defeated, Torinn Rhogar identifies a hidden postwar pattern...
      3347     "godly_reward_item_name": "Avatar Prime Instrument of the Sky Wardens",                                 
      3350     "completion_state": "The Epochalypse Engine advances to 10/10; The Prime Epochalypse Synod loses one ...


